question_data = [
        {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Music","question":"In 1993, Prince changed his name to an unpronounceable symbol because he was unhappy with his contract with Warner Bros.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
        {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Music","question":"American rapper Dr. Dre actually has a Ph.D. doctorate.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
        {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Music","question":"The song &quot;Stronger Than You&quot; is a single by Estelle, who played Garnet in Steven Universe.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
        {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Music","question":"Scatman John&#039;s real name was John Paul Larkin.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
        {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Music","question":"Michael Jackson wrote The Simpsons song &quot;Do the Bartman&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
        {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Music","question":"Eurobeat is primarily an Italian genre of music.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
        {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Music","question":"A Saxophone is a brass instrument.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
        {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Music","question":"Lead Singer Rivers Cuomo of American rock band Weezer attended Harvard.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
        {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Music","question":"Muse is a British (English) rock band","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
        {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Music","question":"The music group Daft Punk got their name from a negative review they received.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]}
]